- Hey, guys. - Hey.
-嗨  -嗨
We need to talk about something.
我们有点事和你们谈谈
Yeah. We don't feel like
我们觉得
we can host Thanksgiving this year.
今年我们不能再作东感恩节晚餐了
- What... - Are you kidding?
-什么... -你是在开玩笑吧
Well, it's just with work and the stress of adoption...
连带工作  还有领养孩子的压力
...we don't feel like we have the energy.
我们只是觉得没有精力弄了
Plus, we don't think it's fair
而且每年都让我们受累
that every year the burden falls on us.
这不公平
That doesn't sound like you.
这口气不像你啊
That's Monica talking.
这像是莫妮卡的话
No, no, we made this decision together.
不  不  这是我们两个人的决定
She's putting words in your mouth.
你把她放你嘴里的话  又说了一遍
Don't you put words in people's mouths.
你不应该把话放到我们口中
You put turkey in people's mouths.
而是把火鸡放到我们口中
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
This is Emma's first Thanksgiving.
这可是艾玛的第一个感恩节
No, it's not.
才不是...
It's not? When was she born?
不是吗  她什么时候出生的
Well, personally,
我个人认为
I think it's great you're giving yourself a break.
你们是应该休息一下子了
Thank you, Pheebs.
谢谢  菲比
Sure. It's just as well.
不客气  这样倒好
I mean, last year wasn't very good.
我是说  去年的晚餐也没那么好
I think she's losing her touch.
她已江郎才尽  今年不会更好了
What? You are way off, lady.
什么  你大错特错了  女士
Am l? Really? Am l?
是么  真的吗  是么
Well, why don't you cook Thanksgiving dinner
那你就再做一次感恩节大餐
and prove me wrong.
证明我错了
Well, think about it.
你好好想想
You'd be trying to top what you did last year.
你这是在跟去年的你比拼
You'd be in competition with yourself.
你是在和...自己竞争
That's my favorite kind.
大爱啊
Okay, we are doing this.
好吧  今年我们继续
Don't let yourself get manipulated this way.
别让自己这么容易被左右
Stay out of this, Chandler.
不关你的事  钱德勒
This is between me and me.
这是"我"和"我"之间的事情
We are supposed to
这件事
make these decisions together.
我们应该一起决定啊
Dr. Phi:一档帮人解决家庭问题的脱口秀
还记得我给你录的菲尔医生怎么说的么
《老友记》第十季第八集 感恩节晚餐大家都迟到了
《老友记》  第十季  第8集 感恩节晚餐大家都迟到了
- Hey. - Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
-嗨  -嗨  感恩节快乐
Happy Needless Turkey-Murder Day.
火鸡殉难日快乐
You guys, I ordered some chocolate pies
我从布利克
from that bakery on Bleeker.
订了些巧克力派
Could you pick them up for me?
你们能帮我去取回来么
You're not making the pies?
你不自己作派吗
I don't make chocolate pies.
不  我不做巧克力派的
When I was younger,
我小时候
I entered this pie-eating contest.
参加过一个吃派比赛
I ate so many
吃得太多了
that the thought of them makes me sick.
导致我一想就恶心
Did you at least win the contest?
那你赢了没有
Two minutes, twelve pies and a part of one tin.
两分钟吃了12个外加1片
Okay, I'll see you guys at 4.
好吧  我们4点见
Can't wait.
很让人期待哦
This dinner is gonna be so great.
今年的晚餐一定棒极了
In your face, last-year me.
去年的莫妮卡  我要你好看
- Hey, Rach? - Yeah.
-嗨  瑞秋  -嗯
What's Emma doing today?
艾玛今天的行程是什么
Well, let's see,
我们看看啊
I know that she has a meeting with her lawyer...
我只知道她今天要和律师见面
...and then she has to make a very big poop.
然后呢  她要拉个大便
Why?
怎么了
Well, I want to enter her in a baby pageant.
我想让她参加婴儿选美
Oh, my God.
哦  天呐
That's the creepiest thing I've ever heard.
这是我听说过的最让人毛骨悚然的事情了
Okay, but before you say no,
在你拒绝之前  听我说
my friend Suzanne is entering her kid.
我朋友苏珊娜带她的孩子参加了
And compared to Emma,
和艾玛比起来
she's a real dog.
那小家伙就像只小狗
Phoebe, all babies are beautiful.
哦  菲比  所有孩子都是美丽的
Oh, okay.
好吧
No. Phoebe,
不  菲比
just the idea of pitting one baby against another...
难道我们只是为了一个奖杯
...l mean, you know,
就把孩子们比来比去
and judging who's cuter just for a trophy...
决定谁更漂亮
And a thousand dollars.
还有一千块奖金
...is something I'm very interested in.
对此我很感兴趣
Oh, please, do not tell Ross.
对了  千万别告诉罗斯
He still believes that
他还是相信
what's on the inside is important.
内在的东西才重要
Okay. And Emma needs a cowgirl outfit
对了艾玛得
for the competition.
穿牛仔装参加比赛
Where am I gonna get a cowgirl outfit on Thanksgiving?
感恩节我上哪儿找牛仔装啊
Well, I was thinking--
我在想...
Take the clothes off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid!
把乔伊的椰菜娃娃的衣服扒了
Did someone drop the baton again?
又有人把指挥棒给掉了
Why come all the way from Kansas
为什么从堪萨斯那么老远来
to do that?
就为了做这个
I don't get older, I just get better.
老娘不是越来越老  而是越来越好
You know what just occurred to me?
你知道我刚想到什么
This could be our last Thanksgiving
这可能是最后一次
just the two of us.
只有我们两个人一起过感恩节了
I mean, we could be getting a baby soon.
我是说  我们很快就会有个孩子了
You don't know that.
你怎么知道
Somebody's gonna pick us.
有人会选择我们的
But we haven't heard a thing
可是这几周
from the adoption agency.
我们都没收到领养消息
I'm telling you, it's gonna happen.
我告诉你  肯定会的
Next year,
明年会是
it's gonna be you, me and little Hemingway Bing.
你我还有小海明威·宾
What? He's my favorite author.
干嘛  他是我最喜欢的作家
Name one of his books.
说出他一本书的名字
The Firm?
《企业》
Okay, let's see. Okay, the turkey's in the oven.
好吧  火鸡已经在烤箱里了
The stuffing is ready.
添料也准备好了
You know,
你知道么
you always cook this meal all by yourself.
你总是自己弄这些东西
Let me help this year.
今年让我帮帮你吧
Oh, Chandler, that's sweet.
钱德勒  这太好了
But you don't have to do everything Dr. Phil tells you to do.
但你不用一直按菲尔医生说的做
I'm serious, let me do something.
我是认真的  让我做点什么吧
Just not the turkey. Nothing high-profile.
不是给火鸡填馅  做点不难的东西  .
Okay, let's see.
我想想...
Oh, the cranberry sauce.
啊  酸梅酱
It's easy to make,
很容易做
and no one really cares about it.
而且大家也不是很在意那东西
Tell me more.
还有呢
I'm gonna go check on something across the hall.
我去对门儿检查别的
You start by washing these.
你先把这个洗干净吧
Not with soap!
别用洗涤剂
You obviously haven't tasted my Palmolive potatoes.
你肯定没吃过我沐浴液洗过的土豆
Hi. Hey, guess what Joey has.
嘿  猜猜乔伊拿到了什么
Three tickets to today's Rangers game!
三张今天纽约流浪者的票
Dude, I wanted him to guess.
兄弟  我是让他猜的
Oh, my God.
哦  天哪
Yeah, they're great seats too.
是啊  而且都是好座位哦
Guess where they are.
猜猜什么位置
Center ice.
正中间
Did I do something to you?
我是不是和你有什么过节
The game's at 1.
比赛一点开始
So?
怎样
Dinner's at 4. We'll never make it back.
晚饭四点开始  我们赶不回来的
So we'll leave before it's over.
那我们就提前退场
We'll be back in time.
我们会准时回来的
You said that now.
你现在这么说
But it could take us a long time to get back home.
可是到时候必定要花很多时间回来的
Plus, Joey could get lost
另外乔伊可能会迷路
and they could have to page us to go pick him up.
他们还得喊我们把他领会来
Dude, two times that happened!
老兄  事不过三
Look, Monica's been working hard all day.
莫妮卡为了做晚饭忙了一整天
She didn't want to host in the first place.
她一开始的时候是不想做的
We shouldn't go.
我们不该去的
He's right, man.
他说得没错儿
Yeah, I guess. So we'll see you at 4.
好吧  那么四点钟见
Okay.
嗯
And get ready to taste
准备好品尝
my very special cranberries.
我的特制酸梅酱哦
Or should I say "Chan-berries"?
或者  应该叫做"钱式酸梅"
That's some gentle comedy, dude.
伙计  你真够搞笑的
We're still going to the game, right?
我们还是要去看比赛的  对吧
Yeah.
是的
Hey.
嘿
Phoebe, listen, I think we gotta go.
菲比  我想走了
This place is freaking me out.
这地方让我坐立不安
I've been watching this guy over there.
你看到那边那个人了么
I don't think he came with a kid.
我可不认为他带来的是个孩子
But we can't leave now.
但你现在不能离开啊
There was this one baby, Haley,
有一个叫黑利的小孩
who was favored to win...
是夺冠的大热门
...she got croup, so she had to stay home.
得了哮喘  不得不待在家里
This competition just blew wide-open, folks.
这次比赛才大开方便之门  家长们
Phoebe, it's just too weird.
菲比  这太奇怪了
I just saw a 1 -year-old with pantyhose on.
我看见一个一岁的小孩穿连裤袜
Oh, I know. We should've been more prepared.
我知道  我们准备的确实不够充分
It's okay. Now, the way I see it,
没事儿  我觉得
our real competition now is Cameron.
咱们最有力的竞争对手是卡梅伦
My God, they just took her sweater off.
天呐  她的衣服被脱掉了
Michelin Man:著名轮胎的卡通形象
看他的手臂  你好  米其林先生
Phoebe, come on.
菲比
You know what, it's already 3:00.
已经都三点了
They haven't even gotten to Emma's group yet.
他们还没有评审到艾玛这一组
We got dinner.
我们该走了  回去吃饭
But Emma's got what it takes.
但是艾玛的条件都具备了
She could go all the way!
她一定能走到最后
Phoebe, you have to calm down.
菲比  冷静点
Okay.
好吧
Rachel, the hottest babies in the tri-state area
瑞秋  三州交界地区
are in this room right now.
最漂亮的宝贝们都在这里了
I overheard a judge say
而我听见一个评审说
that not one of them holds a candle to Emma.
没人比得过艾玛
- Really? - Yeah.
-真的么  -没错
You heard him say that?
你听见他们这么说
Yeah.
对
All right. Okay. All right,
好吧  那就让我们
let's give these babies something to cry about.
给其他的孩子们一点悲惨的回忆
Good. Let's get down to business.
太好了  开工吧
Emma needs some makeup.
艾玛需要化妆
What?
什么
She's gonna look washed-out next to the others.
不化妆跟其它孩子比起来会逊色三分的
No, Phoebe, I'm not letting you put makeup on my baby.
菲比  我不会让你给我的孩子化妆的
Why not?
为什么不
Because I already did.
因为我已经给她化过了
You suck! Get off the ice, you idiot!
太逊了  快下场吧  你个白痴
- What a game. - I know. Yeah.
-太精彩了  -没错  耶
I can't believe Chandler's missing this.
钱德勒错过了这场比赛真遗憾啊
I'm sorry he's not here.
我也替他觉得遗憾
But I gotta say,
但我不得不说
I am really enjoying nacho chair.
我真的很喜欢这个"玉米片"座
Yeah, I'd probably enjoy it more
嗯  要是你不总是把我的手打开
if you didn't keep batting my hand away.
我也许会更喜欢些
These seats are great.
这位置太棒了
I know, I know.
是啊  没错
When I was here for "Holidays on lce" ...
上次在这看假期冰上节目
...l was sitting so far away,
座位太远了
Michelle Kwan couldn't read my banner.
关颖珊根本就看不到我举的条幅
We'd better get going.
我们该走了啦
If we don't leave now, we're gonna be late.
现在不走  回去吃饭就晚了
But it's a tie game.
可比赛太精彩了
So we're a little late.
回去晚点应该可以吧
The girls will be there.
女生们会在那的
Let's just stay for one more goal.
再进一个球再走啦
- I don't know. - One more fight.
-不好吧  -再有人打一架
- Okay. - Okay.
-好吧  -好吧
Where is everybody?
大家都哪里去了
They're 45 minutes late.
他们迟到了45分钟
I can't believe they're not here.
我真不敢相信他们还没来
I slave and I slave for what?
我那么辛苦这一天是为了什么
They've ruined Cranberry Day.
他们毁了我的酸梅酱日
How late are we?
我们迟到了多久
Forty-five minutes.
45分钟
- Here. - Okay.
-给  -好的.
Rachel and Phoebe are already there,
瑞秋和菲比应该已经到了
so they probably started without us.
所以他们可能已经开始了
We could just slip in,
我们溜进去
and no one needs to know where we were.
这样谁都不会注意我们的
You may want to lose the foam finger.
你不把这个泡沫大手指扔掉么
Oh, no, no, no.
哦  才不呢
You just want to put it on your hand.
你只是想把它套在你手上
You're not at Thanksgiving?
你们没在里面
No, we're late.
没  我们迟到了
What are you doing here?
你们在这里干什么
We're late too.
我们也迟到了
We figured we could be late
我们本以为我们可以迟到
because you'd be on time.
因为你们会准时到
Don't point that thing at me, Tribbiani.
别用这个指着我  姓崔的
So nobody's here?
那...里面没人
Monica's gonna kill us.
莫妮卡会杀了我们的
Yeah, where were you?
你们到什么地方去了
Yeah, what's with the trophy?
奖杯怎么来的
Well, we were at a spelling bee.
嗯  我们去参加拼字大赛了
And I won.
我赢了
You won an adult
你在感恩节这天
Thanksgiving Day spelling bee?
赢得了一场成人拼字游戏
Yes. Y-E-S. Yes.
是  Y-E-S  是
Let me see this.
让我看看...
"Grand Supreme Little Darling, New York Division"?
纽约区超级无敌小可爱
That's me.
那便是我
You entered Emma in a beauty pageant?
你们让艾玛参加了选美比赛
And it looks like she put makeup on her.
而且看起来她还给她化了妆
Wait a second...
等等...
Where have I seen that cowgirl outfit before?
我好像在什么地方见过这身牛仔...
I can't believe this.
无法置信
She's our daughter.
她是我们的女儿
That you would treat her like some kind of show dog
你把她当成观赏狗一样
is inexcusable.
不可饶恕
She won a thousand dollars.
她为我们赢得了一千美元
So this is an annual thing?
这比赛是一年一次的吗
That's Alicia May Emory's outfit!
啊  这是艾莉西亚·梅·埃默里的服装
Guys, there are people in there
伙计们  有人在里面
who are not getting any happier.
要发火了
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办
I don't know, you guys figure it out.
我不知道  你们想办法
I gotta put Emma down for a nap.
我先把艾玛送回去睡觉
And, Rach, while you're in there,
哦  瑞秋  你进去
throw something on Alicia May.
给艾莉西亚·梅穿件衣服
All right, what are we gonna say?
好吧  我们该怎么说
We'll say that we were mugged.
我们可以说  我们被抢劫了
You can't get mad at someone
当有人被抢了的时候
who's been mugged.
你怎么还会生他气
Good. But you don't look like you were mugged.
不错  但你看起来不像被抢过
No. Here.
不像  这样才像
Hey!
嘿
Do you hear something?
你有没有听到什么
- They're out there. - Let me see.
-他们都在外面  -让我看看
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
They're an hour late,
他们迟到了一小时
and they're just standing there talking.
还在那里聊天
Everything's so distorted.
一切都乱套了
It looks like Joey has a giant hand.
乔伊有只大手
That says "Rangers" on it.
上面写"流浪者"
They went to the game.
他们去看比赛了
Oh, they are in for a world of pain.
这下我饶不了他们
Ross' shirt is torn.
罗斯的衬衫撕坏了
They're late and they're sloppy.
他们不但迟到  而且衣衫不整
All right, Emma's napping.
好了  艾玛睡下了
What happened to your shirt?
你的衬衫怎么了
I got mugged,
我被抢了
and they stole my pocket.
他们还抢走了我的口袋
We're just trying to figure out an excuse.
我们是在找借口
How about this?
这样如何
We could say that
我们可以说
Monica told us 5:00, not 4:00.
莫妮卡告诉我们是5点  而不是4点
That way we're right on time.
这样我们就没迟到而且很准时
Or we could plant PCP in the apartment
或者  我们可以在房间里藏些迷药
and call the cops on her.
打电话让警察把她抓了
That would be a good way
嗯  这的确是个
to get rid of all the PCP we have lying around.
下迷药的好办法
We'll just say that she said it was 5:00.
你可以就说她说的是5点
We'll just act casual.
保持自然些
We're not late, we're right on time.
所以我们根本没有迟到
"We know you're out there."
"我们知道你们在外面"
Who do you think it's from?
你觉得这是谁写的
Oh, God, this is bad. This is so bad.
天啊  糟了  简直太糟了
Well, let's just go in there and face them.
好吧  让我们进去面对他们吧
I'm not going in first.
我不要先进去
I bet that vein on Monica's forehead is popping like crazy.
莫妮卡前额上的青筋肯定快爆裂了
I hate that thing.
我也讨厌啊
It's like a bolt of lightning.
那张脸就像扭曲的闪电一样
I have an idea.
我有主意了
Why don't we play Rock, Paper, Scissors,
我们可以玩石头剪子布
and whoever loses, goes in first.
输了的先进去
- All right, I'm in. - Ready.
-好吧  我参加  -准备
I win.
啊  我赢了
What is that?
这是什么
That's fire. It beats everything.
火焰  赢过一切
Oh, really? Does it beat water balloon?
真的么  能赢过一个水球么
Well-played, Phoebe Buffay. Well-played.
好极了  菲比·布菲  玩得真好
All right, enough,
好啦好啦
let's all go in at the same time.
让我们一起进去算了
- Okay. - Okay.
-好  -好
It's locked.
锁住了
What? Oh, sure, now they lock it.
什么  他们现在倒把门锁上了
When they're having sex
当他们在沙发上做爱时
on the couch, it's like:
就像是在说
"Come on in, my butt is surprisingly hairy!"
"快进来  快进来  我的屁股上毛好多  "
All right, come on. All right, you guys,
好吧  别闹了  里面的两位
we're so sorry we're late.
很抱歉我们迟到了
Please let us in so we can have dinner together.
让我们进去一起吃晚餐吧
No, everything's cold.
不  东西都凉了
The turkey's dried out and the stuffing's all soggy.
火鸡干了  馅也松了
Yeah, and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that's--
嗯  而且那碗酸梅酱也……
What happens to cranberry sauce?
酸梅酱怎么了
Nothing, it's fine.
没事儿  很好
Oh, thank God.
哦  谢天谢地
Come on, you guys, we're sorry.
好啦  伙计们  真的抱歉
Our subway broke down.
回来的路上  地铁坏了
That's a lie!
说谎
You went to the game.
你们去看比赛了
I can see Joey's hand.
我能看到乔伊的手
For the love of God, take it off!
我说过了让你把它扔掉了
Guys, it doesn't matter why we're late.
伙计们  我们是否迟到了并不重要
We're all here now.
重要的是我们都到了
Please let us in so we can
让我们进去
have some of your delicious turkey.
吃美味的火鸡吧
I had a dream once
我曾经做梦
about a fax machine that did that.
传真机可以这样
That's all the turkey you're gonna get.
这就是你们能得的火鸡
How are we gonna decide who gets this?
怎么决定谁吃
Water balloon!
水球
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办啊
I'm starving.
我饿死了
I just remembered,
哦  对了  我想起来了
we do have something to eat.
我们有吃的了
Monica put something
今天早晨莫妮卡
in our oven this morning.
放了点东西在炉子里面
You touch that, and you will be sorry!
嘿  动了它你们会后悔的
Guys, I'd listen to her.
伙计们  最好听她的
The vein is bigger than I've ever seen it!
她的血管涨到前所未有的大
Oh, my God, it's Brussels sprouts!
天呐  是甘蓝菜
That's worse than no food.
这是什么嘛  不能吃的
All you got was Monica's stinky Brussels sprouts.
啊哈  你们只有莫妮卡的发臭甘蓝菜
Stinky?
发臭的
Please let me stay on this side of the door.
请让我呆在门的这一边
Oh, I know! I still have my old key.
对了  我还有以前的钥匙呢
We can just unlock the door.
我们可以直接把门打开
I don't know if that's a good idea.
我不觉得这是个好主意
They don't wanna be with us.
他们明显不想和我们在一起
You know what.
你知道么
I don't wanna be with them either...
我也不想和他们一起
...but it's Thanksgiving,
但今天是感恩节
and we should not want to be together together.
不想在一起也要在一起
If I could just get in there,
让我们进去
make a face-to-face apology...
面对面的道歉吧
...look them in the eye,
看到我的眼睛
I could get them to forgive us.
他们就会原谅我的
I don't know.
我不确定
I'm telling you...
我告诉你...
...l can do it.
我做得到
Yeah, he can do it.
嗯  他做得到
It all looks so beautiful.
看起来太美味了
The turkey, the stuffing.
那火鸡  那填料
The cranberries.
那酸梅酱呢
Enough! A monkey could've made them.
够了  猴子都会做
Hey, listen, guys, we feel really terrible.
听我说  我们真得很抱歉
He's doing that weird eye-contact thing.
他又来那什么"目光接触"了
Don't look at him.
别看他
Come on, you guys.
听我说  伙计们
We want you to know we're very, very sorry.
我们想让你们了解  我们真的  真的很抱歉
Right, guys?
对吧  伙计们
- I feel terrible. - Oh, so sorry.
-真的很抱歉  -非常  对不起
But let's not ruin this day.
我们别毁掉这美好的一天啊
You've worked so hard.
你们如此之辛劳
Let's move past this
让我们忘了这件事
and try to have a nice meal all together, huh?
一起吃一顿美好的晚餐吧
The floating heads do make a good point.
那些漂浮着的脑袋好像说得没错
Yeah, they do seem to feel pretty bad.
是啊  他们真的好像很抱歉
So bad.
非常抱歉
Okay.
好吧
Okay, you two go get the dessert,
好吧  你们两个去拿甜品来
and I'll let you in.
我让你们进来
Dessert?
甜品
Yeah, I asked you and Phoebe to pick up the pies.
是啊  我让你和菲比去取派
You did remember, right?
你们记得的  对吧
pies与prize发音近似  菲比利用这点插科打诨
"派"啊  我们以为是"奖"
Here.
给你
"Grand Supreme Little Darling"?
超级无敌小可爱
Congratulations!
恭喜
Oh, my God, you forgot the pies?
天呐  你忘了拿派
Well, I cannot believe this.
真不敢相信
You forced me to make dinner,
你们强迫我做饭
you're an hour late...
又迟到一小时
...and you forget the one little thing
居然还忘记了
that I asked you to do.
我叫你们做的那一点点小事
Really, girls, not cool.
真的  女孩子们  这就是你们不对了
Well, you man-heads aren't any better.
好吧  你们男人又好到哪里去
You lied about going to the game.
你们说谎  去看比赛
You knew it'd make you late,
明知道会迟到
and you went anyway.
还坚持要去
Hey, I'm getting a little tired of this.
我有点烦了
We said we're sorry.
我们都道歉了
It's Thanksgiving, for Pete's sakes!
今天是感恩节
A day of forgiveness.
是原谅之日
It's a day to be thankful.
是感激之日吧
Don't make me come up there!
小心我上去敲你
It's too late for apologies.
现在道歉太晚了
Fine, let's just go.
好吧  我们走
I don't need your stupid dinner.
我们可以不在这里吃饭
That would be a lot more convincing
如果你没流口水的话
if you weren't drooling.
你的话可能更可信点
Oh, is that what that is?
哦  原来是你的口水
Sorry.
对不起
Come on, you guys, let's just do our own Thanksgiving.
伙计们  我们自己准备感恩节晚餐吧
Yeah, I'll cook.
好  我做饭
Yeah, let's go out.
好  出去吃
Yeah, you three have a nice Thanksgiving.
你们三个  感恩节快乐
The three of us?
我们三个
Yeah. You, Chan and the vein.
你  钱德勒  还有你的"血管"
I'm stuck.
啊  我被卡住了
Joey, that is not gonna work.
乔伊  这招不管用的
No, seriously.
不  我是认真的
I'm really wedged in here.
我真的被卡住了
I'll pull you through.
我把你拉出来
Okay.
好
Stop.
住手
I'm worried about damaging my head.
我担心会弄伤我的头
It's a little late for that.
现在说太晚了
Hurry up, you gotta do something.
快点  帮帮忙啊
All right, well, this does not change anything.
这不会改变什么的
We need to get something
我们需要点东西
to grease the sides of his face
让他两边的脸润滑一些
We got turkey grease.
我们有火鸡汁
Bring it.
拿来
I just want to say that I'm sorry
我很抱歉
I referred to the vein as a separate person.
还把"血管"说成了一个人
Here you go.
倒了
Oh, that smells good.
味道不错
- Okay? - Okay, try it.
-好了吗  -好  试试看
It isn't working.
没用
We're gonna have to unscrew the chain.
我们必须把链条卸下来了
Hurry, I can't feel my ears.
快点  我都感觉不到我的耳朵了
Can you ever feel your ears?
你曾经感觉到过耳朵么
Interesting.
有意思
Chandler, where are your tools?
钱德勒  你的工具哪里去了
Oh, I left them on my bulldozer.
啊  我把他们落到推土机上了
I don't have tools.
我根本也没有工具啊
Well, I do, but Rachel borrowed them.
我有  但被瑞秋借去了
I lent them to Ross.
我借给了罗斯
I gave them to Joey.
我给了乔伊
I left them at the park.
我留在车库了
I'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.
还真忍不住想逗他
I stuffed Brussels sprouts down his pants.
我早就给他裤子里放了甘蓝菜
Nice.
很好
Okay, I have to get that.
好  我去接电话
Now, when I get back,
当我回来的时候
I want you and your friends to be gone.
我希望你和你的朋友们已经离开了
Thanksgiving is over.
感恩节完了
The vein has spoken.
"血管"说话了
It's really starting to hurt.
我的头真的被卡住了
Look, I'm gonna pull on the door...
好吧  我会拉门
...and you guys push.
然后你们努力推
Maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out, okay?
这样可能他就有足够的空隙出来了  好吧
Okay, so push.
好  推吧
Just a sec.
等下
We're kind of in the middle of something here.
我们正忙着
Hey, stop putting things down my pants.
别往我的裤子里面放东西
Come on, guys, push!
来吧  伙计们  推吧
Yeah, come on, push!
来  推  推  推
Push! Push!
推  推
My cranberries!
我的酸梅酱
Man, I got food all over me.
我全身都是吃的了
I can't believe what you did.
真不敢相信会这样
Monica's gonna kill you.
莫妮卡会杀了你的
Look! Look! Look
看  看  看
what the-- Look what the floating heads did!
这个"漂脑袋"做了什么
I don't care.
没关系
What's going on?
怎么了
That was the adoption agency.
是领养中心处打来的
And?
然后
We're getting a baby!
我们可以领养孩子了
Are you serious?!
真的么
There's a pregnant woman in Ohio,
有个俄亥俄州的孕妇
and she picked us.
选了我们
Oh, my God, that's great!
天呐  太棒了
That's incredible.
难以置信
I'm so happy for you.
太为你们高兴了
This Thanksgiving kicks last Thanksgiving's ass!
今年的感恩节比去年好太多了
To Monica and Chandler
敬莫妮卡和钱德勒
and that knocked-up girl in Ohio.
还有那俄亥俄州的不小心怀孕的女孩
I'm just so happy
你们两个终于要有孩子了
you guys are finally getting a kid.
这真让我高兴
I know. Have you considered pageanting?
你们没考虑过去游行
I can't believe they called.
真不敢相信他们打电话来了
I mean, we're actually getting a baby.
我们就会有孩子了
I know how you feel.
我能体会你们的感受
- Really? - Sure.
-真的么  -当然啦
I went through the exact same thing
买艾莉西亚·梅·埃默里时
with Alicia May Emory.
我经历过完全相同的事情
The waiting, the wondering.
那种期待  那种迷茫
Then one day,
直到有一天
I get that call from Toys"R"Us.
我接到了玩具公司的电话
She was in stock.
她又有货了
That is the exact same thing.
确实"完全相同"